I have, at this point, a four-person company.
That's all I need.
But with AI, I have 1,000 four-person companies.
These things are now autonomous.
By next year, I'll have 10,000—
10,000 four-person companies that can help me
and support my clients.
In November 2022, ChatGPT came out.
And I took a two-week vacation, and I sat on my couch
with my phone, with my computer,
and I just played for two weeks.
And I was like, this—this is now the time.
Having loved technology and been part of that story
my whole life, I knew this was the time.
On most things that we do on a computer,
the AI is right more than humans.
Does it still make mistakes? Sure.
Are you going to give up your sovereignty to the AI,
or do you want to use it as a tool?
Do you want it to teach you to be smarter and better,
or do all of your thinking for you?